<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jdmurphy.org on</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/</link><description>Recent content in jdmurphy.org on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.jdmurphy.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/bullfighters-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/bullfighters-rules/</guid><description>Bullfighter Rules 0.1.1 Never leave the house without a camera Never leave the house without making your bed Never talk directly into the camera Never begin a sentence with “I, me, my” Start tomorrow, tonight Go to bed tired Dress appropriately and in a way that makes you feel confident Say no Say yes Show up early Smile Ask for help Say “I don’t know” Ask others about themselves Stay late Stay for dinner and drinks Hope for the future Own your process Show your work Never make excuses Complete one task at a time Delete all the apps from your phone except for texting/calling/contacts, navigation/transportation, and music Use your computer as a terminal Back up footage in three places - an internal drive, an external drive, and a cloud drive Reinvent yourself until you are the best in the world at what you do Be someone people want to work with Start projects people want to work on Sleep eight hours a night Wake up early every morning Think every morning Work out every day Read books every day Read classic and contemporary literature, books on history, architecture, sociology, psychology, religion, art, and design Go to used bookstores Go to local coffee shops Go to independent movie theatres Watch old movies Watch bad movies Watch with the director’s commentary Carry a notebook (or two) Keep a calendar Keep a to-do list Keep a journal Wear a uniform Keep an overnight bag in your car Minimize monthly expenses Make do without until you can afford the nice version of something When buying gifts, buy a nice version of a cheap thing rather than a cheap version of a nice thing Learn gun safety Learn to cook on a camping stove Learn to wash your clothes in the sink Learn to give stick and poke tattoos Learn card games Learn to change your mind Learn many skills Learn one craft Learn your tools Do things that scare you Tend a garden Travel as far as you can, as often as you can Learn how to find interesting things everywhere you go Learn to act graciously and appropriately around the very poor and very rich Give generously Love with abandon Speak concisely Never take credit Sometimes take blame Always take initiative Think slow Decide fast Don’t tell anyone what you’re going to do Show people what you’ve done Use your life all the way up Sources:</description></item><item><title>23-7-12</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-12/</guid><description>Last Post: [[23-7-9]]
 On a work trip in Williamsburg, VA. Really really pleased with how the site is starting to shape up.</description></item><item><title>23-7-14</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-14/</guid><description>Last post: [[23-7-12]]
 In Gettysburg, PA for work today. This tour has been pretty insane so far. Saw some amazing things and we are far from done but I am so tired.</description></item><item><title>23-7-15</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-15/</guid><description>Previous post: [[23-7-14]]
 Touring Valley Forge, PA on a tour bus. Interesting stuff. My DIY Film School program will be called Full Stack Filmmaking - free, open source film school.</description></item><item><title>23-7-19</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-19/</guid><description>At Blank Street Coffee in Arlinglinton, VA. Have been working on the east coast since the 9th, so I am super super tired.</description></item><item><title>23-7-9</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/blog/23-7-9/</guid><description>Finally had a breakthrough on the digital garden idea I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to build for ages. Markdown based, editable in VSCode or Obsidian, global graph, homepage featuring recent notes, and hosted via GitHub pages.</description></item><item><title>Art vs Design</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/Art-vs-Design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/Art-vs-Design/</guid><description>This is something I&amp;rsquo;ve been ruminating on for a long time.
Art is talking, design is listening.
Design is empathy for the future.</description></item><item><title>Diagram Films</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/Diagram-Films/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/Diagram-Films/</guid><description>The Imperfectionist Logline: A series of &amp;ldquo;how-to&amp;rdquo; videos in the style of Van Neistat/Tom Sachs (industrial/essay) about improving my life - starting from 0.</description></item><item><title>Library</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/Library/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/Library/</guid><description> Author Title Release Date Medium Format Anderson, Wes Rushmore 1998-12-11 Film Blu-ray Anderson, Wes Rushmore 1998-12-11 Screenplay Paperback Vinterberg, Thomas The Celebration 1998-06-19 Film Blu-ray</description></item><item><title>paper journaling system</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/paper-journaling-system/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/paper-journaling-system/</guid><description>How to set up the perfect journal:
Purchase the Clairfontaine My.Essential A5 in dot grid Purchase the Leuchtturm1917 Classic Pen loop Open the notebook and attach the pen loop to the inside back cover at the top in the center Write &amp;ldquo;(month/year) calendar&amp;rdquo; at the top left corner of the first available page, oriented portrait Write &amp;ldquo;(month/year) habit tracker&amp;rdquo; at the top left corner of the next available page, oriented landscape COMPLETE LATER!</description></item><item><title>Video Ideas</title><link>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/Video-Ideas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jdmurphy.org/notes/Video-Ideas/</guid><description>How to be an imperfectionist How to fold a fitted sheet How to wake up at 5am every morning How to exercise every day How to read every day How to write every day How to quit eating sugar How to build habits and discipline How to be a filmmakaer How to be an architect How to be a game developer How to go back to college How to learn how to draw How to learn how to learn The lessons developers learned from Breath of the Wild, and what I hope they learn from tears of the kingdom Stories that can only be told in games The aesthetics of homebrew games The aesthetics of iOS Jailbreaking Richard Linklater: Sculpting in Time Werner Herzog&amp;rsquo;s Rogue Film School Applying Tom Sachs&amp;rsquo; Ten Bullets to my real life Magical Realism in America - How We Talk About the places we live Kentucky Route Zero, American Gods, Twin Peaks, Gravity Falls Walking to Designing the Criterion Collection of Video Games Bioshock Shadow of the Colossus The Last of Us Collection Earthbound Ico Firewatch Myst Beyond Good and Evil Death Stranding Kentucy Route Zero Grim Fandango Celeste The Stanley Parable Okami Portal and Portal 2 Half Life Collection Mirror&amp;rsquo;s Edge Cave Story Control Max Payne Elden Ring Dishonored Collection Red Dead Redemption Collection Outer Wilds Art Project Ideas</description></item></channel></rss>